{
    "subject": "resource/Sister_Act",
    "predicate": "property/writer",
    "object": "resource/Paul_Rudnick",
    "human_readable": "The writer of Sister Act is Paul Rudnick.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.907360315322876,
            "question": "Besides Sister Act, what other works has Paul Rudnick written?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8265102505683899,
            "question": "Name the screenwriter of Sister Act."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6352649331092834,
            "question": "Paul Rudnick is known for writing which movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6327624320983887,
            "question": "Is Paul Rudnick known primarily for writing comedies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6252806782722473,
            "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for Sister Act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5636982321739197,
            "question": "What is the name of the person who wrote the screenplay for Sister Act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41048091650009155,
            "question": "What film did Paul Rudnick write the screenplay for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37983784079551697,
            "question": "What genre is Sister Act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33062905073165894,
            "question": "Has Paul Rudnick won any awards for his screenwriting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2003364861011505,
            "question": "What year was Sister Act released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The writer of Sister Act is Paul Rudnick.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3310_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Paul Rudnick won any awards for his screenwriting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3310_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Sister Act?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3310_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film did Paul Rudnick write the screenplay for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3310_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3310_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3310_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3310_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3310_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3310_168.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3310_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3310_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3310_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3310_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3310_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Sister Act\" was written by Paul Rudnick, thus supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}